

# **Jason Rostar**

Web Developer, Programmer, & Designer

Military Veteran with an inactive Secret Security Clearance and over 9 years of proven experience in the United States Navy. Possess a comprehensive background in full stack web development, administration and creative problem solving derived from conducting domestic and global operations in multiple countries worldwide. Recipient of awards for outstanding performance and professionalism. Career supported by the active pursuit of Lambda School Full Stack Web Development program.

Grants Pass, OR www.jasonrostar.net

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JavaScript/HTML5/CSS3 SCSS/LESS/Material UI NodeJS/Express/Knex Unit/Integration/End-to-End

Testing

ReactJS/Redux/Context SQL/SQLite/MySQL Python/CS Version Control/Git

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# United States Navy

Security Team Lead

06/2016 - 05/2019

- Lead Petty Officer of Miramar Brig Security Team. Comprised of five Soldiers and Marines, responsible for providing a safe working environment for the installation of over 8 million dollars in state-of-the-art security cameras and touch-screen monitors.
- Received a Navy Marine Corps Achievement Medal for outstanding service over the 3 year period working at the Miramar, California Brig.
- Actively pursued bachelors degree from Central Michigan University and Department of Labor office management certificate.

## **United States Navy**

Aviation Maintenance Administration

02/2010 - 05/2016 Various Locations

- Utilized database administration knowledge by maintaining server and database security and data integrity, creating and managing user log-in accounts, managing hardware and software upgrades, which resulted in over 1000 mishap-free flight hours during deployments.
- Implemented and administered Local Area Networks (LAN) aboard U.S. Navy ships to support maintenance and flight operations contributing to the mission success of two West Pacific deployments.
- Managed an inventory of over 500 items; accurate accounting and upkeep resulted in the saving of over \$1M in maintenance costs for the Navy.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Science (B.S.) degree - Organizational and Business Administration

Central Michigan University, Mount Pleasant, Mi

08/2019

- Formally educated in skills pertaining to the legal environment of business, communication, public relations, human resources, organizational psychology, and management through best practices.

## **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

https://jasonrostar.github.io/ExtendedResume/ (08/2019 - Present)

Regularly updated with new styling and layouts to provide potential employers access to copies of certificates, awards, resume and degree.

https://github.com/JasonRostar (08/2016 - Present)

- Regularly updated with new projects created with tools such as ReactJS, NodeJS, HTML5 and CSS3.

# **CERTIFICATES**

Oracle 11g Database - Syracuse University 🗗

Office Manager/Administrative Services - Department of Labor - Certificate of Completion of Apprenticeship 🗷

Computer Operator - Department of Labor - Certificate of Completion of Apprenticeship 🗷